<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CodeZero</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on CodeZero</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Reed Clayton</title>
      <link>/team/reed_clayton/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/reed_clayton/</guid>
      <description>Reed is a seasoned entrepreneurial, adaptable technology leader with more than 19 years of experience in fintech, payments and enterprise software. Reed has a track record of building, growing and managing teams and strategy, having consistently delivered double-digit revenue growth YoY across multiple organizations and industry verticals.
Most recently, Reed is the CEO at Traxitt, a platform that helps industrial companies integrate connected sensors to unlock big data insights, machine learning and predictive maintenance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>David Shore</title>
      <link>/team/david_shore/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/david_shore/</guid>
      <description>David is a start-up entrepreneur with a corporate finance background focusing on the technology sector. Most recently, David co-founded Traxitt in 2018, a platform that helps industrial companies integrate connected sensors to unlock big data insights, machine learning and predictive maintenance.
Prior to Traxitt, David co-founded Mojio in 2012, the leading platform for connecting cars with over 700,000 monthly subscribers in 8 countries and growing. As Mojio’s CFO, he led multiple financings totalling over $75M and resulting in a current post-money valuation of over $200M.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Narayan Sainaney</title>
      <link>/team/narayan_sainaney/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/narayan_sainaney/</guid>
      <description>Narayan has been a technologist since he was eleven years old and has built several start-ups from the ground up and continues to be involved in a number of new ventures. He co-founded Mindquake Software, Digital Snaps, and Vitrium Systems and currently advises a number of technology firms including Lentil.ai and Moeda Inc.
Prior to Traxitt, Narayan co-founded Mojio in 2012, the leading platform for connecting cars with over 700,000 monthly subscribers in 8 countries and growing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/privacy/</guid>
      <description>CODEZERO PRIVACY POLICY CodeZero Technologies Inc., (“we”/”us”), is committed to protecting your privacy. We make the CodeZero website, Hub and Marketplace located at www.codezero.io, including all subpages and successor pages (together the “Site”) available together with our content, software and services as further described in the CodeZero Terms of Service located at www.codezero.io/tos (the “CodeZero Offerings”). This Privacy Policy describes how we collect, use and disclose information about our users through the Site and in respect of the CodeZero Offerings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms of Service</title>
      <link>/terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/terms/</guid>
      <description>CODEZERO TERMS OF SERVICE Date of Last Update: May 28, 2020
CODE ZERO TECHNOLOGIES INC (‘CODEZERO”/” WE”/”US”) OWNS AND OPERATES THE WEBSITE LOCATED AT WWW.CODEZERO.IO (THE “SITE”) WHICH INCLUDES ACCESS FOR REGISTERED USERS TO AN ELECTRONIC MARKETPLACE THROUGH WHICH USERS CAN OFFER, SELL AND PURCHASE ACCESS TO SOFTWARE APPLICATIONS OF CODEZERO AND THIRD-PARTY VENDORS (“PUBLISHERS”). THESE TERMS OF SERVICE (“TERMS”) APPLY TO ANYONE ACCESSING OR USING THE SITE INCLUDING USERS WHO SIGN UP TO USE THE CODEZERO MARKETPLACE, EITHER AS PUBLISHERS AND/OR AS PURCHASERS OF APPS.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>