<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Team on Traxitt</title>
    <link>/team/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Team on Traxitt</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/team/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Reed Clayton</title>
      <link>/team/reed_clayton/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/reed_clayton/</guid>
      <description>Reed is a seasoned entrepreneurial, adaptable technology leader with more than 19 years of experience in fintech, payments and enterprise software. Reed has a track record of building, growing and managing teams and strategy, having consistently delivered double-digit revenue growth YoY across multiple organizations and industry verticals.
Most recently, Reed is the CEO at Traxitt, a platform that helps industrial companies integrate connected sensors to unlock big data insights, machine learning and predictive maintenance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>David Shore</title>
      <link>/team/david_shore/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/david_shore/</guid>
      <description>David is a start-up entrepreneur with a corporate finance background focusing on the technology sector. Most recently, David co-founded Traxitt in 2018, a platform that helps industrial companies integrate connected sensors to unlock big data insights, machine learning and predictive maintenance.
Prior to Traxitt, David co-founded Mojio in 2012, the leading platform for connecting cars with over 700,000 monthly subscribers in 8 countries and growing. As Mojio’s CFO, he led multiple financings totalling over $75M and resulting in a current post-money valuation of over $200M.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Narayan Sainaney</title>
      <link>/team/narayan_sainaney/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/narayan_sainaney/</guid>
      <description>Narayan has been a technologist since he was eleven years old and has built several start-ups from the ground up and continues to be involved in a number of new ventures. He co-founded Mindquake Software, Digital Snaps, and Vitrium Systems and currently advises a number of technology firms including Lentil.ai and Moeda Inc.
Prior to Traxitt, Narayan co-founded Mojio in 2012, the leading platform for connecting cars with over 700,000 monthly subscribers in 8 countries and growing.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>